{"basic": {
      
"001": {
      "front": "How many different NBA teams has LeBron James played for?",
      "back": "Two"
},

"002": {
      "front": "What is LeBron's nickname?",
      "back": "King James"

},
"003": {
      "front": "How many championships has LeBron won?",
      "back": "Three"

},
"004": {
      "front": "Where is LeBron James from?",
      "back": "Akron, OH"

},
"005": {
      "front": "How many championships have the Cleveland Cavaliers won?",
      "back": "One"

}

},

"clozed": {
      
"001": {
      "front": "LeBron James has played for ... different NBA teams.",

      "back": "two"
      
},
"002": {
      "front": "LeBron's nickname is ... .",
      "back": "King James"

},
"003": {
      "front": "LeBron has won ... championships.",
      "back": "three"

},
"004": {
      "front": "LeBron James is from ... .",
      "back": "Akron, OH"

},
"005": {
      "front": "The Cleveland Cavaliers have won ... championship.",
      "back": "one"

      }
}
